reporo.com 2017-09-03

# Reporo - Privacy Policy – Support

**1\. Introduction**

Reporo (the 'Company') respects the privacy of all of our users, partners and affiliates. We focus on protecting the personal information of internet, mobile internet and mobile application users that interact with us. We pride ourselves on being a responsible company within the mobile advertising ecosystem.

This Privacy Policy is publicly available for all of our users and discloses the ways in which information is gathered, how it is secured, and how we apply it to the service we propose to our customers.

The advertising inventory of our publisher partners (‘Publishers’) is made available on our mobile advertising platform via the User Interface, the ‘Dashboard’. Via the Dashboard our Publishers are able to conveniently sell their inventory and expand their potential value. At the same time, our ad-buying partners (‘Advertisers’) are given the facility to reach target audiences and meet CPA and conversion targets and effectively deliver high-performing campaigns. Reporo complies to all laws and industry guidelines in relation to our privacy practices.

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our website or services or transacting business with us. By using our website and services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**2\. Best practices and targeted advertising**

Reporo endeavours to keep our Publisher and Advertiser partners fully informed of developments in our ad serving capabilities, methods, targeting and best practices and, wherever possible, provide them the option to opt-out of certain types of advertising.

Due to the limitation in available technologies used in mobile advertising compared to that of online/desktop advertising, targeting and opt-out solutions are limited in the mobile ecosystem. Therefore Reporo encourages users to review the privacy policies of mobile optimised websites and applications that they use. You can obtain more information about managing these privacy preferences by reviewing the information shared on the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) website. 

**3\. How we collect information**

This Privacy Policy aims to inform our users and partners why certain information is being collected for advertising purposes. In order to deliver relevant ads to the mobile phone users by our Advertiser partners, our Publishers may transfer specific information to our Ad Serving platform. The information from the Publisher’s traffic, once they’ve interacted with our Ad Serving Platform, may systematically be passed on or may otherwise be accessible on the advertising request. In every possible instance, Reporo confirms with our Publishers that they have been given approval to pass on such information to our Advertisers. At Reporo we are consistently developing the functionality of our Ad Serving Platform and work with our partners to improve the overall experience of the mobile ad consumers.

**4\. Information we receive from our Publishers**

**4.1 Device IDs and NPII**

To enable us to track and deliver effective mobile advertising campaigns that target certain devices and/or countries, Reporo makes use of anonymous mobile device identifiers. These ‘Device IDs’ which maintain the user’s anonymity are made accessible by our Publishers and may be sent with an ad request. They may also be used to ensure the same ad is not delivered to the same mobile device multiple times within a certain time frame.

Other Non-Personally Identifiable Information (NPII) may be sent by Publisher and developers to Reporo with an advertising request while conforming to Publisher privacy practices and notices.

If this information is stored for advertising purposes, at no point can Reporo or its partners use these Device IDs or NPII to uniquely identify an individual. Nor does it use such information to create ‘end-user profiles’.

**5\. Information collected Directly by Reporo and Third-Parties**

In order to track the performance of an advertising campaign, Reporo may collect other NPII about how the users receive and interact with the advertising, such as calculating clicks and conversion ratios.

Reporo may additionally partner up with third parties whom have their own methods of identifying a device. This may be used in the ways previously described, or in some instances, to support third party data for targeted advertising solutions. The information provided by third parties may be in addition to what Publishers may provide or is otherwise accessible to Reporo and may include details of past browsing of end-users to help deliver more relevant ads to the user.

At no point, when working with third parties, does Reporo accept, collect or store Personally Identifiable Information.

**5.1 Personally Identifiable Information**

Any identification of individuals is strictly prohibited as a result of Reporo’s agreements with our Publishers which forbid the passing of Personal Identifiable Information that alone or in combination can help uniquely identify a user.

**5.2 Other Information Available from the Ad Request.**

There is other information that may be collected by Reporo to assist the effective serving of advertising to different mobile devices. This information is passed from the device via the mobile site that is being visited and may include details of the operating system and device model, mobile operator and IP address.

**6\. Cookies**

We use Cookies (unique identifiers that we transfer to your device to enable our systems to recognise your device) to provide features such as traffic optimisation _,_ frequency capping and Remarketing (see below). Using cookies enables us to detect if a device has been encountered before and thus not repeatedly serve the same ad within a certain time frame. This is unless the user’s browser settings prohibit the use of cookies.

Cookies may also be used to facilitate third-party targeting services, including Google (whose services we use) and other performance tracking features.This allows us to make special offers and continue to market our Advertiser's services to those who have shown interest. 

**7\. Remarketing**

Reporo.com uses these Third-Party vendor remarketing tracking cookies, including the Google Adwords tracking cookie. This means we will continue to show ads to you across the internet, specifically on the Google Content Network (GCN). As always we respect your privacy and are not collecting any identifiable information through the use of Google’s or any other Third-Party remarketing system.

**7.1 Remarketing: Advertiser Requirements**

Advertisers using Reporo Remarketing are required to update their website's privacy policy in accordance with [Google's guidelines.](https://support.google.com/adwords/answer/2549063?hl=en)

**8\. Opt-Out:**

With Cookies and Device IDs, Reporo offers users the ability to opt out of these types of interest-based advertising by clicking on the link in our [Opt Out Page](http://rad.reporo.net/prefs.).

You may also opt out other use of cookies by visiting the links below:  
\- Google’s use of cookies: [Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated).  
\- Other third-party vendor’s use of cookies: [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed).

**9\. Updates and Changes to Reporo Privacy Policy**

This policy may be updated to provide further information regarding the use of new technical developments in the evolving mobile advertising ecosystem. In this instance and when required, Reporo will exercise the right to change or update this Privacy Policy. Whenever doing so we will submit a public notice will on our corporate site [www.reporo.com.](http://www.mobads.xn--com-nga/)

Reporo will endeavour to update the Policy at least 30 days prior to any material change required in our practices or this Policy.

**10\. Reporo T &Cs**

To view our full Terms and Conditions please see Terms & Conditions.

**11\. Contacting Reporo**

You may contact Reporo regarding any questions in relation to this privacy policy via email at support@reporo.com.
